{
    "id": "282c55d658ca4698bd3ba1fe9d7e59d8",
    "title": "Personal and reflexive pronouns exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f68afc6014e94782889f818b78d9f539",
            "title": "Personal And Reflexive Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It is ………………….. car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "my",
                        "mine"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That coat is …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "my",
                        "mine"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ……………….. party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "his",
                        "him",
                        "himself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is quite fond of praising ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her",
                        "herself",
                        "hers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That must be ……………….. dog.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "their",
                        "theirs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You must have a word with ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "him",
                        "himself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He did it …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "him",
                        "himself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Whose bag is this?’ ‘It’s …………………’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her",
                        "hers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My dog is an Alsatian. ………………… is a Doberman.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Their",
                        "Theirs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………… took the baby to the hospital.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her",
                        "hers",
                        "herself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t believe ………………. story.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "your",
                        "yours"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mind ………………….. own business.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "your"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw it with …………………. own eyes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "my",
                        "mine"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}